achooallergy.com 2016-06-29

# Privacy Policy | AchooAllergy.com

This Privacy Policy applies to http://www.achooallergy.com owned and operated by achoo! ALLERGY & AIR Products, Inc. ("AchooAllergy.com"). This Privacy Policy describes how achoo! ALLERGY & AIR Products, Inc. collects and uses the personal information you provide. It also describes the choices available to you regarding the use of, your access to, and how to update and correct your personal information.

achoo! ALLERGY & AIR Products, Inc. has received TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and our practices have been reviewed for compliance with the TRUSTe program viewable on the validation page available by clicking the TRUSTe seal. The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through this website, http://www.achooallergy.com and does not cover information that may be collected through software downloaded from the website.

If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact TRUSTe at <https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request>.

AchooAllergy.com knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. This notice describes our privacy policy. By visiting our website AchooAllergy.com you are accepting the practices described in our Privacy Policy.

**What Personally Identifiable Information About Customers Does AchooAllergy.com Gather?  
**  
The information we learn from customers helps us personalize and continually improve your shopping experience at AchooAllergy.com. We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will never sell or rent this information to anyone. Here are the types of information we gather.

Information You Give Us: We receive and store any information you enter on our Web site or give us in any other way. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future shopping for you, improving our store, and communicating with you.

If you choose to contact us on our return/exchange or sales inquiry forms, we request certain personally identifiable information from you on those forms. You must provide contact information (such as name, email and order number). We use this information to respond to your inquiries and process any service requests.

We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.

We request information from you on our order form. To buy from us, you must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we'll use this information to contact you.

We collect the following personally identifiable information from you about your contacts or friends: email address, mailing address, phone number and use the information to fulfill your order.

We use collected information primarily to fulfill customer orders and requests. We do not share this information with any third parties. However, we may disclose personally identifiable information collected if we have received your permission beforehand or in very special circumstances, such as when we believe that such disclosure is required by law or other special cases described below.  
Information provided during the checkout process is collected on our secure servers. That information is then used for final processing of your order. This information includes ordering information such as shipping and billing names and addresses, phone numbers, email addresses and credit card information.

Automatic Information: We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many Web sites, we use "cookies," and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses AchooAllergy.com.

**Newsletters and eBlasts**

Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy. You may opt out of these communications at any time by following the instructions at the top of every email we send or by contacting us at 1-800-339-7123.

To sign up for our newsletter, visit AchooAllergy.com and fill in the [email signup form](https://www.achooallergy.com/newsletter).

**What About Tracking Technologies?**

As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data.

â€“We do not link this automatically collected data to other information we collect about you. 

We achoo! ALLERGY & AIR Products, Inc. and our partners (e.g. marketing partners), affiliates, or analytics or service providers (e.g. Google Analytics, AddThis, Constant Contact, Bing, BuySafe), use technologies such as cookies, beacons, tags, and scripts, to analyze trends, administer the website, tracking usersâ€™ movements around the website, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual and aggregated basis.

We use cookies for our shopping cart, to remember usersâ€™ settings (e.g. language preference), for authentication. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our website, but your ability to use some features or areas of our website may be limited.

Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our website or to display advertising based upon your web browsing activity also use Flash cookies or HTML5 to collect and store information. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5. To manage Flash cookies, please click here: http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html

**Legal Disclosure**

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site. If AchooAllery.com is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personally identifiable information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personally identifiable information.

**Does AchooAllergy.com Share the Information It Receives?**

Absolutely not. Information about our customers is the most important part of our business, and we are not in the business of selling it to others. We will never rent, sell or share your personally identifiable information. We will share your personally identifiable information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy policy

**Service Providers**

We use outside shipping companies to ship orders, and a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. We use an outside company for marketing and analytics. We also use an outside company to host our Website. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes beyond filling your order.

**How Secure Is Information About Me?**

We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personally identifiable information submitted to us, both during transmission and once it is received. We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input.

It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.

We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.

Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page.

While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.

**Updating Personally Identifiable Information**

Users of AchooAllergy.com can update/change or delete their personally identifiable information by calling customer service at 1-800-339-7123 or by sending an email to cs@achooallergy.com. Users may request access to their personally identifiable information for the purpose of correcting, updating and/or deleting it. We will respond to your request within a reasonable timeframe.

**Data Retention**

AchooAllergy.com will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services, please contact us at 1-800-339-7123. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

**Which Information Can I Access?  
**  
AchooAllergy.com gives you access to a broad range of information about your account and your interactions with AchooAllergy.com for the limited purpose of viewing and, in certain cases, updating that information. Returning customers may access their account by clicking on the My Account button on the home page.

**Children**

AchooAllergy.com does not sell products for purchase by children. We sell children's products for purchase by adults. If you are under 18, you may use AchooAllergy.com only with the involvement of a parent or guardian.

**Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions**

If you choose to visit AchooAllergy.com, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our User Agreement, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the state of Georgia. If you have any concern about privacy at AchooAllergy.com, please contact us with a thorough description, and we will try to resolve it.

**Blog**

If you use the blog feature on our site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums. To request removal of your personally identifiable information from our blog, contact us at info@achooallergy.com. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personally identifiable information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why. We reserve the right to terminate the accounts of visitors who use these services in a manner inconsistent with our Terms of Use.

**Social Media Widgets**

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook button and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Web site. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing the feature.

**Behavioral Targeting / Re-Targeting**

We partner with a third party ad network to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our ad network partner uses cookies and Web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information about your activities on this and other Web sites to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt-out by clicking [here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/). You will continue to receive generic ads.

**Links to 3rd Party Sites**

Our Web site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of AchooAllergy.com. If you submit personally identifiable information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any Web site you visit.

**Changes to Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy policy, the home page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page prior to the change becoming effective.

**Company Address**

AchooAllergy.com  
1620-D Satellite Blvd.  
Duluth, GA 30097  
1-800-339-7123  
cs@achooallergy.com

**Privacy Policy Last Updated on: 11/06/2015**
